domainpower.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy | DomainPower

Bidtellect, Inc. (“Bidtellect”, “we”, “us” or “our”) is a digital advertising platform that delivers sponsored content also known as “native content” to third party websites or applications. This Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service forms an agreement between you and Bidtellect for your use of the Website and Services. Collection of your personal information and data is governed by the Bidtellect Privacy Policy in effect at the time the information is collected or processed. This Privacy Policy may be changed at any time and without notice to you by updating this page.

Click on the links below to jump to each section of this Policy:

  1. Scope of Privacy Policy
  2. Customers
  3. Advertising Platform & Collecting User Data
  4. User Options
  5. How We Protect and Retain Your Information
  6. General Provisions
  7. Modification of This Policy
  8. How To Contact Us

## Scope of Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy discloses the privacy and data collection practices associated with Bidtellect’s corporate website at [www.bidtellect.com](https://www.bidtellect.com/) “Website” and the desktop and mobile services that we and our affiliates and business partners provide to advertisers on Bidtellect’s native content advertising platforms, and how we share personal information and data with our vendors and affiliates (“Service Providers”). 

The use we make of the Information, including Personal Information, collected through the Sites and Services may vary depending on whether the information comes from (i) a Bidtellect customer (“Customer”), i.e., an advertiser, or other content provider with whom we have a contractual relationship or (ii) a visitor of our Customers’ websites who interacts with our Services (“User”). Therefore, we have distinguished the relevant information that relates to each of these target categories into three different sections below. Information that is relevant to all three categories is set forth in Section 4 of this Privacy Policy.

We define “Personal Information” to mean personally identifiable information about an individual, such as a name, address, email address, phone number, or other identifier that permits direct or indirect identification of a specific individual, or as otherwise defined by applicable privacy and data security laws. We also treat cookieID, Mobile Ad ID (IDFA/AAID), and IP address as “Personal Information” as defined by the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

Use of our Sites or Services and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes. 

## Customers

### Information That We Collect

We collect Customer Information directly from our Customers based on actions taken directly by the Customer. 

To access restricted sections of the Website, subscribe to email newsletters, request more information about Bidtellect or Services, and/or obtain Services, a Customer will explicitly provide us with personally identifiable information and we may collect data that helps us identify the Customer on the Website. One may choose not to provide such Personal Information to us by not registering on the Website. The Personal Information collected includes:

  * first and last name
  * email address
  * password
  * telephone number
  * computer IP address
  * mobile device unique ID
  * real-time geographic information

### How We Use Customer Data

If a Customer registers for a user account, we may use the Personal Information to send emails or other communications that relate to administration of the user account, use of the Website and Services, and promotional materials about products and services. If the Customer decides at any time to no longer receive email or communications from us, he/she may follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of the communications or contact privacy@bidtellect.com. If the Customer unsubscribes but does not close the account, he/she will still receive administrative emails about the account.

### Customer Information Disclosure

We do not disclose high value Personal Information to any vendor or subprocessor outside of Bidtellect.

### Customer Options

A Customer may access, verify, correct, update or request deletion of the Personal Information in the user account profile by emailing support@bidtellect.com. If the Customer registered to use the Website, he/she is solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the account login and password and for restricting access to his/her computer, and agrees to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under the account and password. We reserve the right to refuse to provide Services, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in our sole discretion.

## Advertising Platform & Collecting User Data

### Information That We Collect

As part of our digital advertising platform and reporting Services, we and our Service Providers log page views and collect anonymous information about activities and interactions on the Website, third party websites, and in mobile apps for the purpose of delivering ads or providing advertising-related services, including providing a specific advertisement based on a particular type of browser or time of day, statistical reporting in connection with the activity on a website or app, and tracking the number of ads served on a particular day to a particular website or app. 

We collect Information through a User’s use of our Services through cookies and other technologies, like most other web-based services when provided User consent. This Information may include, without limitation, information about a User’s operating system, IP address, the web pages accessed by Users within our Customers’ websites, the link that led a User to a Customers’ website, the dates and times a User accesses a Customers’ website, user identifiers such a cookies/MAIDs (See Cookie Policy), and general location information (e.g., city and state).

We work with Service Providers that collect additional data and non-personally identifiable information about users who interact with the Website or Services.

### How We Use User Data

The combination of data (Cookie, MAID, IP, and audience [demo & behavioral]) is used for providing our basic service of ad delivery for maximizing advertising effectiveness.

We use this combination of data to target the proper advertising through processes and determination of interests and behaviors in support of personalization of delivery of tailored content for Interest Based Advertising.

Information is also used to improve a unique User’s experience across multiple browsers and devices (such as smartphones, tablets, or display) by providing better targeted ad campaigns to that User. We may identify a User on a mobile device, and may want to provide similar content through other devices that are associated with the same user. To do this, we identify unique Users across devices, or we may sync cookies and identifiers with our service providers to help our Customers enhance their own data and data segments.

### User Information Disclosure

Bidtellect may disclose User Information to vendors, service providers, agents, contractors, or others who perform functions (e.g., data analysis, fraud detection, or measurement) on our behalf.

### Interest-Based Advertising

Through our Services, Bidtellect may provide tailored advertisements based on the User’s consumption behavior across different Customer Websites, browsers, or devices. For example, if a User visits a website categorized within the automobile industry, the User might see Automobile-related content or ads on another site. In order to tailor advertisements to the User for products and services in which the User might be interested, we employ the use of cookies, JavaScript, tags, HTML5, and other technologies that track the User’s activities online, etc., such as persistent identifiers, web pixels, pixel tags, flash cookies, user data files, locally shared objects/LSO’s, and clear gifs (collectively, “Cookies”). 

For more information about how we use these technologies, please refer to our Cookie Policy. 

We may also use third parties such as data analytics companies, which are third parties that provide data analysis and consumption metrics based on a User’s visits to websites and the behaviors around that activity. This information will be used to adjust targeting and optimization of advertisements to Users for products and services in which they have shown greater interest. Third-party ad network providers or traffic measurement services may also use cookies, JavaScript, tags, and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of ads in support of our delivery of ads. These third-party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one.

For questions about our collection and use of data for interest-based advertising purposes, please contact [support@bidtellect.com](mailto:support@bidtellect.com).

#### Third Party Online Advertising

We may use third parties who collect Information about Users through their own cookies, tags, and other technologies regarding their online activities, either on our Sites and/or other websites across the Internet, in an effort to understand User interests and deliver User advertisements that are tailored to User interests. These third parties include measurement, data analytics, and data management platforms that may collect information about when an individual views or interacts with one of their advertisements and may collect information regarding a User’s activities on our Sites and online activities over time and across different Websites. Like most advertisers, Bidtellect places advertisements where we think they will be most relevant to the recipient. One way to do this is by allowing the advertising networks with whom we work to place their own cookies when an individual visits our Sites. This enables the network advertising company to recognize individuals who have previously visited our Sites. When the individual visits a third-party website on which that network advertising company has purchased ad space, the advertising company can then recognize the individual’s interest in Bidtellect and deliver one of our advertisements. 

## User Options

#### Managing a User Account

A User may access and correct Personal Information in his/her user account profile at any time. A User who registers to use this Website is solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of his/her account login and password and for restricting access to his/her computer. 

As a User, you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. We reserve the right to refuse to provide Services, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in their sole discretion.

#### Bidtellect Opt-Out

Bidtellect is committed to providing consumers notice and choice regarding online and mobile privacy. Should a User wish to opt-out of data collection by Bidtellect’s Cookies and interest-based advertising, our opt-out tool is found at [https://www.bidtellect.com/optout](https://www.bidtellect.com/optout).

Our opt-out tool is a Cookie that will honor a User’s privacy preferences for 5 years or longer within our discretion. If a User uses multiple Internet browsers or shares a computer, the opt-out process should be completed for each browser and/or user login. If the User clears Cookies or browser history from the computer, or uses anti-virus or other software to Cookies from the computer, then the opt-out process will need to be repeated. The opt-out tool does not work if the browser is set to ignore Cookies.

To opt out of Cookies from other websites or companies please visit the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), which will allow a User to opt out of seeing targeted ads from us and from other NAI-approved member companies. For mobile opt outs, the NAI provides instructions to engage system-level opt outs in Android, iOS, and Windows Phone environments.

Users in the United States, Canada, and Europe may go to the DAA consumer choice page at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices), the DAAC consumer choice page at [www.youradchoices.ca/choices](http://www.youradchoices.ca/choices), or the EDAA consumer choice page at [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/), for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding their information being used by the companies listed on the DAA, DAAC, or EDAA, consumer choice pages. Opting out from one or more companies listed on the DAA, DAAC, or EDAA consumer choice page will “opt out” a User from those companies’ delivery of targeted content or ads, but it does not mean the User will no longer receive any advertising through our Services or on other websites.

On browsers that are configured to reject cookies, the opt-out may not be effective, since we identify the choice to opt-out based on a cookie delivered to the User. In this case, the User will need to confirm that the browser is configured properly in order for the opt-out to be effective. For a Safari browser on iOS11 or macOS High Sierra, a User must first adjust the Privacy and Security Settings to turn off both “Prevent Cross-Site Tracking” and “Block All Cookies”, and then return to this privacy policy or preferred opt-out platform to reset opt-out preferences. 

Opting out of Cookies does not necessarily mean that the User will no longer see the Services. However, opting out does mean that the Services will be less relevant because it will not be based on information collected about the User or the User’s browsing history.

## How We Protect and Retain Personal Information

We take security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data and Personal Information. These include firewalls and encryption, internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices, and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems.

If we retain data and Personal Information on our systems, we restrict access to data and Personal Information to employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve our Websites, products, and services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations through a signed Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA) and may be subject to discipline, including termination, if they fail to meet these obligations.

We retain identifiable data, which is directly collected for purposes of serving ads, for twenty-eight (28) days from the User’s last interaction with our Services, after which time we de-identify the data by removing unique identifiers or aggregating the data.

We retain aggregated data, which cannot identify an individual or device and is used for purposes of reporting and analysis, for as long as commercially necessary. We keep opt-out information for longer than this period so that we can continue to honor opt-out requests.

Bidtellect reserves the right to delete any or all data and Personal Information that relates to you, the User, at any time and in Bidtellect’s sole discretion, notwithstanding its normal data retention policies. If Bidtellect changes its retention data policies by updating this Privacy Policy, its new policies will apply to all data then retained by Bidtellect.

### California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents who have an established business relationship with us have the right to request that we provide certain information regarding the disclosure of their personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year. To request such information, contact privacy@bidtellect.com. Requests shall only be accepted via this email address. We shall not be responsible for requests made over the telephone or by any other means.

### Law Enforcement

We cooperate with government, law enforcement officials, or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any data and Personal Information about a User to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including subpoenas) to protect the property and rights of Bidtellect or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

### Notice to Non-US Customers and Users

We may transfer Customer or User Information outside the country in which it is collected (e.g., to the United States), which may not offer the same level of protection for Personal Information as the country in which the Customer or User resides; however, Bidtellect provides contractual safeguards to ensure Information is processed in a way that offers an adequate level of protection when it is shared between or among Bidtellect Services and vendors.

By providing Information, including Personal Information, under this Privacy Policy, the Customer or the User expressly consents to the use of such Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of the Information to another country (e.g., the United States).

### COPPA Compliance

Bidtellect adheres to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Rule (COPPA). We do not knowingly collect any data or target an advertisement on a website directed towards on a website directed to children under the age of thirteen (13). If you, a Customer or User, are the parent or guardian of a child under the age of thirteen (13) and have a concern regarding the Information we collect, please contact support@bidtellect.com.

## General Provisions

### How We Use Information

The Information we collect from Customers and Users are used for the purposes as respectively set forth in the sections above, as well as for the following purposes:

  * To better understand how Customers and Users access and use our Site and Services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis; to respond to Customers’, and Users’, desires and preferences; and for other research, analytical, and statistical purposes.

  * To comply with applicable legal obligations, including requests from law enforcement or other governmental entities.

  * To protect our rights and interests and the rights and interests of our Customers, Users, and the general public

### How We Use Information

When we disclose Information with third parties, we require such recipients to agree to only use the Information we share with them in accordance with this Privacy Policy and for no other purpose than those determined by us in line with this Privacy Policy

## Modification of this Policy

This Privacy Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above.

Bidtellect may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy on our Sites.

If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the Information we have previously collected from you, a Customer or User, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on our Sites.

It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often. By continuing to use the Services or this Website or by sharing information with us, you consent to the use of your information as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

For questions or concerns regarding this statement, contact:

Attn: Chief Compliance Officer  
Bidtellect, Inc.  
777 East Atlantic Ave, Suite 312  
Delray Beach, Florida 33483  
Email: privacy@bidtellect.com
